tripzilla.com 2019-05-06

# Privacy Policy

TripZilla Magazine takes your privacy very seriously. We ask that you read this privacy policy carefully as it contains important information about what to expect when TripZilla Magazine collects personal information about you and how TripZilla Magazine will use your personal data.

#### Information Collected from All Visitors to Our Website

We will obtain personal data about you when you visit us. When you visit TripZilla Magazine, we may monitor the use of this Site through the use of cookies and similar tracking devices. For example, we may monitor the number of times you visit our Site or which pages you go to. This information helps us to build a profile of our users. Some of this data will be aggregated or statistical, which means that we will not be able to identify you individually. Please see further the section on “Our Use of Cookies” below.

#### Use of Cookies

Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behaviour information. The information is used to track visitor use of the Site and to compile statistical reports on Site activity. You can set your browser not to accept cookies and the above websites tell you how to remove cookies from your browser.

#### Access to Your Information and Updating / Correcting Your Information

Subject to the exceptions referred to in section 21(2) of the Personal Data Protection Act 2012 (No. 26 of 2012) of Singapore (“PDPA”), you have the right to request a copy of the information that we hold about you. If you would like a copy of some or all of your personal information, you may [contact us](http://magazine.tripzilla.com/contact-us) any time.

We want to ensure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. If any of the information that you have provided to TripZilla Magazine changes, for example if you change your email address or name, please [contact us](http://magazine.tripzilla.com/contact-us) and let us know the correct details. You may ask us, or we may ask you, to correct information, you or we think is inaccurate, and you may also ask us to remove information which is inaccurate.

#### Non-Disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to third parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, as long as these parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours and others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

#### Links to Other Websites

TripZilla Magazine may contain links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website so when you link to other websites you should read their own privacy policies.

#### Sale of Business

If TripZilla Magazine’s business is sold or integrated with another business, your details may be disclosed to our advisers and any prospective purchasers and their advisers and will be passed on to the new owners of the business.

#### Changes to Privacy Policy

We keep our privacy policy under regular review. If we change our privacy policy we will post the changes on this page, and place notices on other pages of the Site, so that you may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it at all times. This privacy policy was last updated on 23rd day of November 2015.

#### How to Contact Us

We welcome your views about TripZilla Magazine and our privacy policy. If you have any queries or comments feel free to [contact us](http://magazine.tripzilla.com/contact-us) anytime.

LAST UPDATED: 23rd day of November 2015
